<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<article desc="usage">
   Double-clicking on the jar will show the following window:
   <img id="tool"/>
   
   <title title="overview" />
   The Window allows to open one or several TrueType or OpenType fonts. Each font will add a new tab:
   <img id="tool" />
   
   <title title="top of the window" />
   The menu bar contains severals menus:
   <ul>
      <li>File menu: allows to open a Font file, or save the characteristics of the selected Font in an html file</li>
      <li>Tools menu: allows to refresh the characteristics of the selected Font after havinf modified it Font size or associated text</li>      
   </ul>
   <img id="toolbar" />
   The toolbar shows the screen resolution in pixels per inch.
   
   <title title="content of each tab for a font" />
   Each tab represents a Font and has two parts:
   <ul>
      <li>The characteristics of the font</li>
      <li>A diagram showing the values for the text chosen for the font</li>      
   </ul>
   
   <title level="2" title="list of characteristics for a font" />
   <moreInfo id="characteristics for a font" />
   This contains:
   <ul>
      <li>Two editable fields allowing to set the size of the Font in points and the text used to compute the associated characteristics</li>
      <li>A non editable table showing the associated characteristics</li>      
   </ul>
   <img id="fontcharacteristics" />
   <messageBox type="info">
      To be able to refresh the content of the table after having modified the Font size or associated text, you must apply the Tools =&gt; Refresh option.
   </messageBox>
   
   The characteristics are all shown in points and mm:
   <ul>
      <li>The font size, which is the same value of the associated editable field</li>
      <li>The font ascent</li>    
      <li>The font descent</li> 
      <li>The font height</li>        
      <li>The font advance value</li>    
      <li>The font leading value</li>    
      <li>The width and height of the text box</li>
   </ul>   
   
   <title level="2" title="diagram for a font" />
   The diagram shows the font characteristics for the selected text:
   <img id="fontdiagram" />

   <cat id="general" />
</article>
